Guide to the Center for Jewish Living records, 1985-2015.
Center for Jewish Living records
- Alpha Subject Files
  - Engle, Moshe, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Engst, Elaine D, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Ennis, Linda, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Erlich, Dr. Howard, 1989-2005 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Ertl, John, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Eskovitz, Rabbi (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Esterow, Milton, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - "Europa", 2008 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Evans, Harold, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Evensen, Darrick, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Everett, Henry J, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Ezergalius, Inta, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Falk, Arthur and Myrna, 1987, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Falk, Dr. George, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Falk, Lawrence, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Fall Creek Real Estate, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Farley, William F, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Farrell's Washer Service, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Fearless Symmetry Corp, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Feeney, Betsy, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Feierstein, Gerald (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Feierstein, Rabbi Milton and Lenore Judy, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Feinberg, Ed, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Feinstein, Edie, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Feinstein, Howard, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Feigen, Richard, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Feit, Hanoch, 2010-2012 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Feldman, Charles, 1988, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Feldman, Howard and Elain, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Feldman, Seymour, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Fellner, Dr Michael and Fredda Ginsberg, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Fenster, Jennifer and Matt, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Fernstein, Sharon, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - The Field Foundation, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Fierstein, Rabbi Jeremy, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Goldstein, Hillel, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Fierstein, Menashe, 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Finan, Gail T, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Finger Lakes Fabricating, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Fink, Rabbi Brian, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Finson, Rabbi Chaim and Shiva, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Firebaugh Francille, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Fireside, Byrne and Harvey, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - The First Albany Corp, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Fischer Bros. and Leslie (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Fischer, David, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Fisher, Max M, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Flaks, Samuel, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Father Flanagans Boys' Home, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Flather, Mary Ellen, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Fleischmann's Yeast Inc, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Flik International Corp, 2003-2005 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Joseph Flihan Co., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Folksbiene Playhouse, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Ford, John, L, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Forster, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Fowler, Annabel (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Fowler, Douglas, 2002, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Foxman, Abraham H, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Frank, Rabbi Hilik and Vared, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Franklin and Marshall College Kosher Program (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Frank, Leo (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Freedman, Samuel G, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Friedlander, Friedlander, Reizes, Joch and Littman, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Freihoffer Baking Co, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - RT French Co, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Freund, Deborah, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Freidman, Elizabeth, Rabbi Joe and Michael, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Freid, Diane, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Friedlander, Michael S (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Freidman, Shulamis and Gil, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Frost and Berenholtz, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Frost, Candice, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Frous, David (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Fruchthandler, Avroham, 1988, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Frumkin, Alan, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Fuller, David, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Gabbai, Rabbi Albert E, 2005, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Gabor, Allen, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Galbut, Russell, 2005, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Gallagher Home Electronics, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Gallagher and Shean Inc, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Ganeles, Ron and Joyce, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Ganz, Sharon, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Ganz, Victor and Sally, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Garen, Adam C, 2012-2015 (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Garfinkel, Chaim, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Garfinkel, Maurice, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Garmaize, Rabbi A (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Garment, Leonard, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Gebremedhin, Kifle G, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Geffen, Sara Jane, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Geldwert, Jacob, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Geller, Alan, 2005, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Geneva Printing, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Geneva, Phil and Associates, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Gent Engineering, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Gerber, Alan J, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Gerber, Jane S, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - Gersch, Alan, 1991-1998 (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Gerston, Mark, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - Giambattista, Gina A, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 151)
  - Gibson, Eileen, 2013-2014 (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - Gilbert, Martin, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - Gillian, Paul, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 154)
  - Gilman, Sander, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - Ginsberg, Rabbi Hirsch, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Ginsburg, Ruth Bader, 1998, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 157)
  - Gioia Pasta Co, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Giuliani, Rudy W, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Glass, Harry, 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Glass, Rabbi Scott L, 1991, 2005, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Glickman, Marty, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Glogower, Rabbi Rod, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - GMB Enterprises Inc, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Gold, Rabbi Ben Zion, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Gold, Ellie (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Gold, Michal Evan and Sarah, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Goldberg, Elisa, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Goldberg, Roger Henry, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 169)
  - Goldberg, Ron, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - Goldberger, Stephen A, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 171)
  - Golder, Rob, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Goldfarb, Joshua and Tamara Petraff, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Goldfarb, Rabbi Morris and Helen, 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Golding, Amit, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 175)
  - Goldman, Gerald (Box 7, Folder 176)
  - Goldstein, Rabbi Avraham, 2005, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 177)
  - Goldstein, Damian, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 178)
  - Godlstein, Francine, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - Goldstein, Jay Alan, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 180)
  - Goldstein, Seth, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Goldstein, Stephanie, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Goldstein, Susan, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Goodfriend, Evelyn G, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Goodman, Robert, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Goodman, Senator Roy, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Goodwin, George M, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Goody, Janice May, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Gordon, Arnold S and Lynne, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Gould, Shelley, 1998-2005 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Grafstein, Neil (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Grafstein, Shlomo, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Grainger, Chris M, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Grapevine, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Gray, Holly M, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Gray and Company, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Grayman, Gershon, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Green-Konneh, Hon. Kim, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - David J Greene Foundation, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Greene, Joshua (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Green, Mitch, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Green, Pinkey, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Greenberg, Jack, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Geenberg, Jon, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Greenberg, Robert, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Greenberger, David, 2011-2013 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Greenblatt, Rachel L, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Greenspan, Rabbi Harry, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Greenwald, David, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Greenwald, Mark (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Greenwald, Shlomo, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Grimes, Woody, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Grinnell Fire Protection, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Gross, Yigal Mordechai, 2011-2012 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Gruber, Ruth Ellen, 1996-2011 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Gruber, Sam, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Grunhaus, Moshe (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Gu, Yu, 2012-2015 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Gur Aryeh Institute, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Gurock, Jeffrey S, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Gurowitz, William, 1988-1990 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - J Gurion Foundation, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Gurwin, Kopel, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Guttman, Leonard, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Gutenberger, John C, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Guzy, Harold M, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Haagen Dats, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Hager, Rabbi Meyer, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Hagood, Trent, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Haims, Joel, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Haine, Peggy (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Haire, Bruce, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Hakim, Lily (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Hama, Reut Bar, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Hamerkaz, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Hammer, Yaakov M, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Hammond, Jane L, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Han-Dee Pak Inc, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Hancock Building Supplies, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Handler Foundation, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Hanukkah, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Bank Hapaolim, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - The Hangovers, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Hanson, Janelle, 2011-2015 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Hardesty, John DH, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Harris, Richard M and Estelle, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Harris, Ronald Samuel, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Harrison, Dan (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Harrison, Harvey (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Hartnett, Philip, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Hassner, Alfred, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Haus, Jason Paul, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Hawes, Vincent J, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Hearth and Home, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Hebrew Day Schools, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Hebrew Union College, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Hecht, Irene, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Hecht, Joseph A, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Hecht, Toby Tucker, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Heinle, Linda, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Heistein, Martin J, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Heitzman, Holly, 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Helfand, Jonathan, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Heller, Ben and Jordan, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Heller, Gila, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Henault, Pascal, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Henner, Benjamin, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Henry, Susan, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Herer, Yale, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Herman, Stacey and Gary, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Hersh, Jerry, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Herskowitz, Yale, 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Theodor Herzl foundation, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Herzog, Ernest, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Herzstein, Robert (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Heslop, Edward, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Higgens, Robert Michaeol (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - High Holidays 5749 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - High Holidays 5752, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Hillel Academy, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Hillel Cornell, 1991, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Hillel Ithaca, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Hillman, Robert, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Hills Drug Store (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Hillside Inn, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Hiltzik, George, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Hinchey, Maurice, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Hirsch, David, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Hirsch, Oren, 1991, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Hirsch, Renie (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Hirschfeld, Abraham, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Hirschler, Gertrude, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Hittleman, Margo, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Hodges, Christopher D, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Hoffman, Rabbi Joshua, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Hoffman, Roald, 2011, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Hofstra University, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Holmen, Robert G, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Holmberg, Galbraith, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Holt, Bob, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Holtzmann, Howard, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Hoover, Douglas, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Honneff, Jim, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Horowitz Margareten Kosher Foods, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Horton Lewis, 1989-1998 (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Hospitality Consulting Services, Inc., 1990 (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Hovanec, Inc, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Houstan, Alanna, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - HSC Associates, 2007-2011 (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Hubbell, Kent (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - Hughes Dining Room, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 131)
  - Hughes, Eileen (Box 8, Folder 132)
  - Hulander, Kurt, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 133)
  - Huling, William, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - Hunsinger, Laura, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 135)
  - Hurewitz, Josh and Miriam Alexander, 1987-1990, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 136)
  - Hurley, Debra, 2006-2015 (Box 8, Folder 137)
  - Hurwitz, Norma, 2008-2012 (Box 8, Folder 138)
  - Huxel, George, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 139)
  - Hyams, Paul, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 140)
  - ID Booth Co. Inc, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 141)
  - Indyk, Leonard, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 142)
  - International Center for Holocaust Studies, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - International Monetary Fund, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - Israel Discount Bank of NY, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 145)
  - Ithaca Hadassah (Box 8, Folder 146)
  - Ithaca Jewish Community (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - Ithaca Journal, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - Ithaca Paint and Decorating, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - Ithaca Self Storage, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - Ithaca Times, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - Itzkowitz, Mark, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - Ivanov, Micheline, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - Ivker, Frances and Barry, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - Jacobs, Elias, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Jacobs, Harold, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Jacobs, Irwin and Joan, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Jacobs, Jack S and Nicole Boxer, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Jankeloqitz, Michael (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Jaquette, John P Jr, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Frontier, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Life at Cornell, 2005, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - The Jewish Museum NYC, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - The Jewish Press, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Publication Society, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Roots in Spain, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Jewish War Veterans, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Jewish Week, 2005, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Joel, Richard, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, Barbara, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Johnson, Buck, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Johnson, Karl and Julie, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Johnson, Rev. Robert, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Joukowsky Family Vacation, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Judaica News, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Judaica Press, Inc, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Jukowitz, Ari, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Jungreis, Tobias, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Harry de Jur Foundation, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Juran, Donald R, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Just, Alexander D, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Kabak, Shara, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Kadner, William and Jane E, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Kahn, Alfred E, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Kahn, Daniel G, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Kahn, David, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Kairey, Julius, 2012, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Kalaf, Ed, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Kalmanson, Camela, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Kaminetzky, Chaim, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Kaminsky, Bill, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Kaminsky, Thomas, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Kaplan, Elissa, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Kaplan, Steven L, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Kaprow, Rabbi Maurice, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Karangelan, Michael, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Karp, Selwyn, 1989-1993 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Katz, David, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Katz, Robert J (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Katz, Steve, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Kauffeld, Richard, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Kaufman, Gerald, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Kaufman, Henry, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Kaunda, Kenneth (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Kaye, Judith, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Kedem, Gil, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Kellman, Robert, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Kempthorne, Dirk, 2008-2015 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Kennedy, Ellen, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Kennedy, Laing (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Kenney, Anne, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Ken's Foods, Inc, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Kepner, Kevin R (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Kerker, Molly, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Kerrigan, James, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Kersh, Rabbi Jonathan, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Kestenbaum, Leonard, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Kertzner, Rabbi Yitzchak, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Killeen, Sean F, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Kimura, Tamami, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Kinstlinger, Robert, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Kirby, Anita, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Klarsfeld, Serge, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Klein, Eliahu (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Klein, Samuel, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Esther A. and Joseph Klingenstein Fund, Inc, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Klinghoffer, Meryl, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Knapp, Steve, 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Knoedler and Co, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Koenig, Ed, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Kohlberg, Jerome Jr, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Kohn, Daniel and Barbara, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Kolanu (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Konvitz, Josef, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Koppel, Paul, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Koppell, Arielle, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Korman, Gerd, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Kosher Certification (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Kosher Meats (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Kotler, Avery, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Kotz, David, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Kouray, Christian, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Koval, Nikki, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Kovary, Ingirn, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Krakow, Doran and Yoni, 2013-2015 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Kramnick, Isaac, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Kraner, Michael (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Krasdale Foods Inc, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Kraut, Benny, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Krumbein, Mina, 1992, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Kravitz, Edward (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Kreitman, Benjamin, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Kronzek, Alan, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - KTAV Publishing, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Kugel, James, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Kunin, Madeline, 1989, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - Kunofsky, Matthew (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Kurtzig, Sandra, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - Kutell, Benjamin, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Kutsher's, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Labor Zionist Alliance, 1988-1991, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - LaFeber, Walter, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - Lainer, Gil, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Lalonde, Murray, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Lamm, Rabbi Dr. Norman, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Landau, Calvin S, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Lander, Bernard, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Landis, Leonard (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Landy, Eric, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Lapins Association, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - The Larson Co, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Lasdun, Rabbi Yoseph (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - Latkes vs Hamantashen, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Latner, Herbert, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Ronald S Lauder Foundation, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Laufer, Gregory (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Lauren, Ralph, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Lauret, Anne, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Lautenberg, Frank, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - Lavian, David, 2012-2015 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Lawler, Edward J, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Lawrence, Rosie (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Lawru's Foods Inc, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - Leahy, Sen. Patrick, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - Lear, Frances, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - Leavitt, Thomas W (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Leff, Joel, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - Leff, Susan, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 134)
  - Lefko, Jordan and Jane, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 135)
  - Lefkovits, Albert M, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 136)
  - Lefrak, Samuel, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 137)
  - Lehman, Jeffrey (Box 9, Folder 138)
  - Leibowitz, Shira, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 139)
  - Leitner, Roberta, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 140)
  - Lempert, Lesly, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 141)
  - Lempkin, Ben, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 142)
  - Lender, Murray, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 143)
  - Lentini, allan, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 144)
  - Leopold, Kevin, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 145)
  - Leopold, Ray, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 146)
  - Lerman, Rhoda, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 147)
  - Leshnick, Victor (Box 9, Folder 148)
  - Bank Leumi, USA, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 149)
  - Leva Bros Co Inc, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 150)
  - Levin, Simon, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 151)
  - Leo Leviton Co Inc, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 152)
  - Levitt, Bruce, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 153)
  - Levy, Aaron Rabbi (Box 9, Folder 154)
  - Levy, Aaron (Box 9, Folder 155)
  - Levy, Julia, 2009-2010 (Box 9, Folder 156)
  - Lewin, Nathan, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 157)
  - Lewinsohn, Gerald (Box 9, Folder 158)
  - Lewis, Helen (Box 9, Folder 159)
  - Libeskind, Daniel, 2004, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 160)
  - Libson, Robert, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 161)
  - Lichtenberg, Barry, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 162)
  - Lieberman, Arthur, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 163)
  - Lieberman, Jenni, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 164)
  - Lieberman, Senator Joseph, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 165)
  - Lindseth, Jon, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 166)
  - Link, Andre, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 167)
  - Linowitz, Sol, 2013-2014 (Box 9, Folder 168)
  - Linz, Mark, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 169)
  - Lipskey, David, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - List, Albert A, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 171)
  - Leowenthal, Lawrence, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 172)
  - Leon Lowenstein Foundation, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 173)
  - Little Old New York, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 174)
  - Long, Martin, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 175)
  - Longin, Thomas, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 176)
  - Lopatin, Uri, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 177)
  - Long Island Jewish World, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 178)
  - Lowery, Judith, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 179)
  - Lubman, David and Aviva, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 180)
  - Lubman, Elizabeth, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 181)
  - Ludsin, Steven, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 182)
  - Moshe Ludmir and Sons, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 183)
  - Luthy, Teal, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 184)
  - Magid, Norman, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Magid, Zalman, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Magnus, Tamar, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Mallett, Linda F, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Malott, Deane W (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Mandel, Rachel, 2015-2016 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Mandelbaum, Rabbi Bernard, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Machtiger, Neal and Elaine, 1990, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Manischewitz, 1989, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Marbach, Ezra, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Mankowitz, Scott, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Marion, Dane (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Mark, Rabbi and Rose, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Maieroni, John, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Marine Midland Loan center, 1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Martinelli, Ricardo, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Martin, Carolyn, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Martin, Lynn, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Master, Alan E, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Marton, Howard, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Marvin Windows, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Marx, Moses, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Matkoff, Rabbi Yehuda, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Matyas, Robert M, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Mauser, Jonath, 2015 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Maxwell, Robert, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Maxwell House Coffee, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - May, Miriam S, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - May, Peter, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - McAvoy, Thomas, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - McCain Foods Inc, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - McCall, H Carl, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - McCarty, Kathleen, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - McFall, Robert, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 34)